rachelaziani.com 2003-04-01

# Terms and Conditions

**Information Collection and Use**   
Nomad Media Inc.(hereby referred to as "we" in the following policy) is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or license this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.   
**Order**   
We request information from the user on our membership form. Here a user must provide contact information (like their email address) and or financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. Order forms are only used for processing orders. Contact information on order forms will be used when a user requests specific information, such as shipping date or the status of a particular item. Financial information is required in an order to process payments. Your email address is requested when a user places an order so that the user can be emailed a permanent receipt, plus any other information that the user may request.   
**IP Address**   
Your IP address is used by Nomad Media Inc. to record your transactions, as well as diagnose problems with our server. Your IP address can also be used to identify you to authorities in the case of fraud.   
**Credit Card Information**   
Your Credit Card information will not be disclosed to any third parties. All information is held in the strictest confidence by Nomad Media Inc. only.   
**Sharing**   
Nomad Media Inc. will not share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. Customer names will not be sold. We will not share your information with third parties although Nomad Media Inc. completely abides by law and will respond to subpoenas, warrants or other court orders regarding information of a particular visitor. Additionally, if a member is believed to be engaged in illegal activity, we reserve the right to report this to law enforcement.   
**Links**   
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.   
**Site and Service Updates**   
We also send the user site and service announcement updates. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email.   
**Correction/Updating Personal Information**   
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as billing information), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support.   
**Notification of Changes**   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.   
**Communications**   
Nomad Media Inc. is internet based and email only to users who request information. The user has the option of not receiving this type of communication by notifying [admin@nomadmediainc.com](mailto:admin@nomadmediainc.com) by email.
